Hello everyone, welcome to my channel.
Today I will introduce the link between Claw and Blender.
This is the project file.
Here you need to record the animation in advance.
After recording, play and check.
Here you need to delete the animation.
Because Blender can't directly identify multiple layers of animation.
Here the setting starts at 30.
Now we need to do UV rendering.
Here we need to do UV rendering.
Click on the UV rendering icon.
Click on Vithub
In this case we choose Video Editor.
Click on Video Editor and spices which is left.
In this case , we set up the re-turb.
It does the work.
Click on Edit.
Adapt including text.
Click on Next.
Add a new text layer.
In the next step, we will do a close-up of the model.
The model will be in FBX format.
The FBX location cannot have Chinese characters.
Then select the virtual model and select all.
Here, select a single target.
If you select multiple targets, it will not contain animation.
Thin, thick, here select thick.
Select the unified UV coordinates.
In the options, select the model action and save animation.
The ratio here is selected because the unit of Blender is rice.
Click OK for other default settings.
Click OK to confirm.
Next, export the animation of the costume.
The costume is exported to Alembic format.
Alembic has two formats.
Here, select Ogawa format.
You can find Owlaye.
Click OK to confirm.
Here, select OCC format.
That's all,
and for the location screen there is no
selection need for the location screen.
Click OK,
then select the location screen,
format to Open Cube Até Showhow.
The default is the time interval between the two data samples. For example, if the default is 2 hours, each two time units, such as seconds or seconds, store one data, and the relative sample value of the needle is the time value, whether it is based on the needle number and not the absolute time, such as seconds.
The unit selects the rice, selects the play area,
and the relative sample value of the needle.
Next, open Blender and press A to select and delete.
First, import the model, click the file and import FBX.
Here you can see that the model has been imported.
Here you need to adjust the animation to be changed to 0.
Then import the costume, also click the file to import Alembic.
Here you need to hide Google.
Next, play the animation to see if there is a problem.
Here you need to hide all variables.
If there is an option option, more formulas to show.
Here you can also expand the animation here.
Like this.
Then you canนol softer tone.
In this way, when the animation isobject, the color name changes.
Next, change the material to check the effect
You need to apply the texture to the clothing application, here switch to the color mode
Here you need to use the node rango plugin
In the edit tab, set the plugin, search for the node plugin
After selecting, you can use, click on the new key, click on the principle, BSDF
Then press CTRL plus SHIFT plus T
Find the previously saved UV image and configure
Here you can adjust the brightness of the face
Next, you can make the scene and the lighting
Here you can make the scene and the lighting
And finally the road
Just click on the light now
If you have any question, leave what you thought in the comment box
The end
Press Shift A to increase the camera
Press the float button to enter the camera view
If you want to adjust the camera view, press and hold the camera view
Select the camera and go to the view
Finally, adjust the camera to the view
Adjust to the rendering mode to check the effect
You can see that it is black now because there is no light source
Here I used HDR as the light source
It is also possible to use HDR as the light source
Switch to the color change to the world environment
In the blank, right-click to increase the texture environment texture
Open your HDR picture on the application and connect the color
Switch to the rendering mode to check the rendering effect
Finally, set the rendering attribute and perform the final rendering
You can see the final result
Thank you for watching
Thank you.